Guide to the Freshman Year, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Central records and records of the dean of the Freshman Year, 1920-1964; Series I
  - Freshman activities fund, 1956-1960 (Box 92, Folder 320 - 322)
  - Freshman activities fund: account book, 1959-1963 (Box 92, Folder 323)
  - Freshman activities fund, 1960-1963 (Box 92, Folder 324 - 326)
  - Freshmen Activities Fund, 1962-1964 (Box 93, Folder 327 - 328)
  - Freshman affairs: confidential statements on freshmen, 1957-1958 (Box 93, Folder 329)
  - Freshman affairs: miscellaneous, 1957-1958 (Box 93, Folder 330)
  - Freshman affairs - academic and otherwise official, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 331)
  - Freshman affairs - counselor comments, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 332)
  - Freshman affairs - extra - curricular, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 333)
  - Freshman affairs - riots, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 334)
  - Freshman affairs - academic and otherwise official, 1959-1960 (Box 93, Folder 335)
  - Freshman affairs - comments of counselors on, 1959-1960 (Box 93, Folder 336)
  - Freshman affairs - extra - curricular, 1959-1960 (Box 93, Folder 337)
  - Freshman affairs - riots, 1959-1960 (Box 93, Folder 338)
  - Freshman affairs - academic & otherwise official, 1960-1961 (Box 93, Folder 339)
  - Freshman affairs - extra curricular, 1960-1961 (Box 93, Folder 340)
  - Freshman affairs: academic and otherwise official, 1961-1962 (Box 93, Folder 341)
  - Freshman affairs: confidential statements on freshman, 1961-1962 (Box 93, Folder 342)
  - Freshman affairs: extra - curricular, 1961-1962 (Box 93, Folder 343)
  - Freshman affairs - academic and otherwise official, 1962-1964 (Box 93, Folder 344 - 345)
  - Freshman affairs - confidential statements, 1963-1964 (Box 93, Folder 346)
  - Freshman assembly addresses, 1951-1957 (Box 93, Folder 347)
  - Freshman days, 1963-1964 (Box 93, Folder 348)
  - Freshman executive committee, 1961-1963 (Box 93, Folder 349 - 350)
  - Freshman night series, 1961-1962 (Box 94, Folder 351)
  - Freshman orientation days, 1962-1964 (Box 94, Folder 352 - 353)
  - Freshman prom: final financial statements, 1958-1959 (Box 94, Folder 354)
  - Freshman prom, 1959-1962 (Box 94, Folder 355 - 357)
  - Freshman week, 1957-1959 (Box 94, Folder 358 - 359)
  - Freshman week: activities fund, 1958-1959 (Box 94, Folder 360)
  - Temporary freshman week, 1959-1960 (Box 94, Folder 361)
  - Freshman week: activities fund, 1959-1960 (Box 94, Folder 362)
  - Freshman week, 1960-1962 (Box 94, Folder 363 - 365)
  - Freshman week, 1961-1962 (Box 95, Folder 366)
  - Future needs, 1957-1963 (Box 95, Folder 367 - 369)
  - G, 1958-1959 (Box 95, Folder 370)
  - Glee club, 1961-1962 (Box 95, Folder 371)
  - Grading, 1962-1963 (Box 95, Folder 372)
  - Gymnasium, 1958-1962 (Box 95, Folder 373)
  - "H", 1958-1964 (Box 95, Folder 374)
  - "Headaches", 1953-1962 (Box 95, Folder 375)
  - Health department, 1958-1964 (Box 95, Folder 376 - 381)
  - Heeling, 1958-1962 (Box 95, Folder 382)
  - History dept, 1962-1964 (Box 95, Folder 383)
  - Honor system, 1951-1959 (Box 95, Folder 384)
  - I, 1958-1959 (Box 95, Folder 385)
  - "Inquiry", 1960-1961 (Box 95, Folder 386)
  - Instructions to instructors, 1958-1964 (Box 95, Folder 387)
  - Insured tuition payment plan, 1958-1961 (Box 96, Folder 388)
  - K, 1958-1959 (Box 96, Folder 389)
  - L, 1958-1961 (Box 96, Folder 390)
  - Lawyers - discussion groups, 1960-1961 (Box 96, Folder 391)
  - Library, 1958-1963 (Box 96, Folder 392)
  - M, 1958-1964 (Box 96, Folder 393)
  - April mailing, 1963-1964 (Box 96, Folder 394)
  - July mailing to students, 1963-1964 (Box 96, Folder 395)
  - "Manners and morals", 1957 (Box 96, Folder 396)
  - M.A.T. program, 1959-1960 (Box 96, Folder 397)
  - Military affairs, committee on, 1954-1955 (Box 96, Folder 398)
  - Miscellaneous, 1958-1959 (Box 96, Folder 399)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence outside of Yale (other universities and colleges), 1958-1962 (Box 96, Folder 400 - 403)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence with other colleges, 1962-1964 (Box 96, Folder 404 - 405)
  - Miscellany, 1958-1964 (Box 96, Folder 406 - 411)
  - Moore fund, 1958-1960 (Box 96, Folder 412 - 413)
  - Moore fund, Paul, 1960-1961 (Box 96, Folder 414)
  - Moore fund, 1961-1962 (Box 96, Folder 415)
  - Moore fund income, 1962-1964 (Box 96, Folder 416 - 417)
  - N, 1961-1962 (Box 96, Folder 418)
  - New england presidents conference, 1958-1959 (Box 96, Folder 419)
  - New england presidents' conference (i.e., Association of colleges in New England), 1959-1962 (Box 96, Folder 420 - 422)
  - New england presidents' conference, 1962-1964 (Box 96, Folder 423 - 424)
  - New Haven Yale Club, 1958-1963 (Box 97, Folder 425 - 429)
  - New York Yale Club freshman prizes, 1958-1959 (Box 97, Folder 430)
  - New York Yale Club freshman prizes (class of 1963), 1959-1960 (Box 97, Folder 431)
  - New York Yale Club freshman prizes (charms), 1960-1961 (Box 97, Folder 432)
  - New York Yale Club freshman prizes, 1961-1964 (Box 97, Folder 433 - 434)
  - News Bureau, 1959-1962 (Box 97, Folder 435)
  - Numbers, 1962-1963 (Box 97, Folder 436)
  - "O", 1958-1961 (Box 97, Folder 437)
  - Office equipment and supplies, 1958-1960 (Box 97, Folder 438 - 439)
  - Office equipment and supplies: requisitions, 1960-1961 (Box 97, Folder 440)
  - Office equipment and supplies, 1961-1962 (Box 97, Folder 441)
  - Office staff: permanent, 1958-1959 (Box 97, Folder 442)
  - Office staff: students (bursary), 1958-1959 (Box 97, Folder 443)
  - Office staff: temporary, 1958-1959 (Box 97, Folder 444)
  - Office staff: permanent, 1959-1960 (Box 98, Folder 445)
  - Office staff: temporary, 1959-1960 (Box 98, Folder 446)
  - Office staff: permanent, 1960-1961 (Box 98, Folder 447)
  - Office staff: temporary, 1960-1961 (Box 98, Folder 448)
  - Office staff: permanent, 1961-1962 (Box 98, Folder 449)
  - Office staff: temporary, 1961-1962 (Box 98, Folder 450)
  - Office staff: permanent, 1962-1963 (Box 98, Folder 451)
  - Office staff: students, bursary, 1962-1963 (Box 98, Folder 452)
  - Office staff: temporary, 1962-1963 (Box 98, Folder 453)
  - Office staff: permanent, 1963-1964 (Box 98, Folder 454)
  - Office staff: students, bursary, 1963-1964 (Box 98, Folder 455)
  - Orientation, 1951-1962 (Box 98, Folder 456 - 458)
  - "P", 1958-1961 (Box 98, Folder 459)
  - Parents - June letter to:, 1963-1964 (Box 98, Folder 460)
  - Parents - September letter to:, 1963-1964 (Box 98, Folder 461)
  - Parents' day, 1958-1964 (Box 98, Folder 462 - 466)
  - Parietal rules committee, 1961-1962 (Box 98, Folder 467)
  - Personnel - faculty statistics, 1951-1957 (Box 98, Folder 468)
  - Personnel policies (faculty and non-faculty), 1959-1962 (Box 98, Folder 469 - 471)
  - Personnel - time schedules, 1920-1954 (Box 99, Folder 472)
  - Phi beta kapp, 1958, 1961 (Box 99, Folder 473)
  - Placement officers, 1958-1962 (Box 99, Folder 474 - 478)
  - Placement officers & placement polices, 1961-1962 (Box 99, Folder 479)
  - Placement officers, 1962-1963 (Box 99, Folder 480)
  - Placement policy - summer, 1963 (Box 99, Folder 481)
  - Placement officers and placement policies, 1963-1964 (Box 99, Folder 482)
  - Planning a course of study (PCS - see secondary schools), 1960-1964 (Box 99, Folder 483)
  - Political seminar, 1958 (Box 99, Folder 484)
  - Positions and recommendations, 1958-1964 (Box 99, Folder 485 - 490)
  - Pre-Medical: all data, 1960-1961 (Box 99, Folder 491)
  - "Pre-Medical" (all data), 1961-1962 (Box 99, Folder 492)
  - Pre-Medical, 1962-1964 (Box 99, Folder 493 - 494)
  - President's committee, 1961-1962 (Box 99, Folder 495)
  - President's committee on Yale - New Haven community relations, 1959-1960 (Box 99, Folder 496)
  - President's office, 1958-1964 (Box 100, Folder 497)
  - President's report, 1958-1963 (Box 100, Folder 498 - 502)
  - Program blanks, 1960-1962 (Box 100, Folder 503)
  - Prom letter to parents, 1961-1962 (Box 100, Folder 504)
  - Prospective freshmen, 1959-1960 (Box 100, Folder 505)
  - Provost's office, 1958-1964 (Box 100, Folder 506 - 511)
  - Provost's committee on future members, 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 512)
  - Publications, undergraduate, 1958-1959 (Box 100, Folder 513)
  - Publications: undergraduate & miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 100, Folder 514)
  - Publications, undergraduate, The Eli Book, 1958-1964 (Box 100, Folder 515 - 520)
  - Publications - "The Gate ----67", 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 521)
  - Publication, undergraduate, The Old Campus, 1958-1960 (Box 100, Folder 522 - 523)
  - The Old Campus, 1960-1964 (Box 100, Folder 524 - 527)
  - Publications, undergraduate: "On the Fence", 1957-1958 (Box 100, Folder 528)
  - "On the Fence": Ken Hill, 1958-1959 (Box 100, Folder 529)
  - Undergraduate publication: "On the Fence", 1959-1960 (Box 100, Folder 530)
  - Publications - "On the Fence", 1959-1960 (Box 100, Folder 531)
  - "On the Fence", 1961-1964 (Box 100, Folder 532 - 533)
  - Publications - university, 1962-1964 (Box 100, Folder 534 - 535)
  - Publications, university - "Planning a Course of Study", 1958-1960 (Box 100, Folder 536 - 537)
  - Publications, university - Undergraduate Courses of Study, 1959-1960 (Box 100, Folder 538)
  - Undergraduate Courses of Study, 1961-1962 (Box 100, Folder 539)
  - Publications - UCS, 1962-1963 (Box 100, Folder 540)
  - Publications - Undergraduate Regulations Bulletin, 1963-1964 (Box 100, Folder 541)
  - Publications, university - miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 100, Folder 542)
  - "R", 1958-1959 (Box 100, Folder 543)
  - Reading list, 1961-1963 (Box 100, Folder 544)
  - Reading office, 1958-1959 (Box 100, Folder 545)
  - Reading office: arithmetic, 1958-1959 (Box 100, Folder 546)
  - Reading Office, 1959-1960 (Box 101, Folder 547)
  - Readmissions, 1953-1955 (Box 101, Folder 548)
  - Recapitulation of Accounts, 1958-1959 (Box 101, Folder 549)
  - Recapitulation of freshman instruction, 1959-1960 (Box 101, Folder 550)
  - Religious activities, 1958-1962 (Box 101, Folder 551)
  - Requisitions, 1962-1963 (Box 101, Folder 552)
  - Research co-ordinating committee, 1960-1961 (Box 101, Folder 553)
  - Reserve list, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 554)
  - Revised distributional credit and college credit awards, 1963-1964 (Box 101, Folder 555)
  - Rules committee, 1958-1961 (Box 101, Folder 556)
  - Rules & regulations (affecting freshmen), 1958-1961 (Box 101, Folder 557)
  - S, 1958-1959 (Box 101, Folder 558)
  - Schedule committee, 1958-1963 (Box 101, Folder 559)
  - Scholarships: general, 1958-1960 (Box 101, Folder 560)
  - Secondary schools, 1958-1959 (Box 101, Folder 561)
  - Secondary schools: (correspondence on planning a course of study), 1958-1961 (Box 101, Folder 562)
  - Secondary schools: miscellaneous, 1959-1962 (Box 101, Folder 563 - 565)
  - Secondary schools, 1962-1963 (Box 102, Folder 566)
  - Secondary schools: class of 1967, 1962-1963 (Box 102, Folder 567)
  - Secondary schools, 1963-1964 (Box 102, Folder 568)
  - Secretary's office, 1959-1964 (Box 102, Folder 569)
  - Selective service, 1959-1964 (Box 102, Folder 570)
  - Senior advisory board, 1958-1964 (Box 102, Folder 571)
  - Senior prom, 1961 (Box 102, Folder 572)
  - Service bureau: miscellaneous, 1958-1962 (Box 102, Folder 573 - 576)
  - Service bureau, 1962-1964 (Box 102, Folder 577 - 578)
  - Shelter procedure, 1962-1963 (Box 102, Folder 579)
  - Social schedule: freshman, 1958-1959 (Box 102, Folder 580)
  - Solicitation, 1959-1962 (Box 102, Folder 581)
  - Sophomore couses (of historical interest), 1922-1954 (Box 102, Folder 582)
  - Sophomore programs, 1958-1959 (Box 102, Folder 583)
  - Sophomore programs: current, 1959-1960 (Box 102, Folder 584)
  - Sophomore programs, 1959-1960 (Box 102, Folder 585)
  - Sophomore programs, 1960-1964 (Box 103, Folder 586 - 589)
  - Dean souter, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 590)
  - Special events and miscellaneous expenses, 1957-1963 (Box 103, Folder 591 - 596)
  - Spring & summer printing, 1963-1964 (Box 103, Folder 597)
  - Statistics, 1958-1961 (Box 103, Folder 598 - 600)
  - Student agency, 1962-1963 (Box 103, Folder 601)
  - Students, alphabetically by counselors with count - September, 1963, 1962-1963 (Box 103, Folder 602)
  - Student records office, 1958-1962 (Box 103, Folder 603 - 607)
  - Study records office, 1963-1964 (Box 103, Folder 608)
  - Study skills institute, 1963-1964 (Box 103, Folder 609)
  - Study skills office, 1960-1961 (Box 103, Folder 610)
  - Study skills office: arithmetic and other, 1960 (Box 103, Folder 611)
  - Study skills office, 1961-1964 (Box 103, Folder 612 - 614)
  - Summer institutes, 1959-1960 (Box 103, Folder 615)
  - Summer schools, 1960-1963 (Box 103, Folder 616 - 617)
  - Summer study skills institute, 1960-1963 (Box 104, Folder 618 - 619)
  - Sundry accounts receivable: recapitulation, 1957-1958 (Box 104, Folder 620)
  - Sundry accounts receivable: Whiteman, completed action, 1958-1959 (Box 104, Folder 621)
  - Sundry accounts receivable: completed action, 1959-1961 (Box 104, Folder 622 - 623)
  - Sundry accounts receivable: requisitions and bills paid and outstanding, 1961-1962 (Box 104, Folder 624)
  - Sundry accounts receivable: 54-00-30-9370, 1962-1964 (Box 104, Folder 625 - 626)
  - Tea - Invitation list, 1963-1964 (Box 104, Folder 627)
  - TV permission, 1960-1961 (Box 104, Folder 628)
  - Television sets, 1961-1962 (Box 104, Folder 629)
  - Testing (including E.T.S.), 1958-1964 (Box 104, Folder 630)
  - Thomas, Ralph Hill, Foundation fellow & lecturer, 1958-1963 (Box 104, Folder 631 - 635)
  - Thomas, Ralph Hill Foundation Fellow and Lecture, 1963-1964 (Box 105, Folder 636)
  - Townand Gown: including president's committee on Yale-New Haven community relations, 1960-1961 (Box 105, Folder 637)
  - Travel expenses, 1958-1963 (Box 105, Folder 638)
  - Travel posters, 1958 (Box 105, Folder 639)
  - Treasurer's office, 1959-1964 (Box 105, Folder 640 - 643)
  - Undergraduate affairs, miscellaneous, 1958-1962 (Box 105, Folder 644 - 646)
  - Undergraduate affairs, 1962-1964 (Box 105, Folder 647 - 648)
  - Undergraduate affairs committee, 1957-1960 (Box 105, Folder 649)
  - Undergraduate: miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 105, Folder 650)
  - Undergraduate organizations, 1963-1964 (Box 105, Folder 651)
  - Undergraduate publications: On the Fence, 1958-1959 (Box 105, Folder 652)
  - Undergraduate Regulation Book, 1960-1961 (Box 105, Folder 653)
  - Undergraduate Regulations Bulletin, 1961-1963 (Box 105, Folder 654 - 655)
  - United World Federalist, 1957-1958 (Box 105, Folder 656)
  - University council, 1962, undated (Box 105, Folder 657)
  - University police, 1962-1964 (Box 106, Folder 658 - 659)
  - Vending machine, 1958-1961 (Box 106, Folder 660)
  - W, 1958-1959 (Box 106, Folder 661)
  - Whiteman, Dean, 1962-1963 (Box 106, Folder 662)
  - Williston conference, 1963-1964 (Box 106, Folder 663)
  - Withdrawals from, and late readmissions to the freshman class, 1958-1962 (Box 106, Folder 664 - 667)
  - Withdrawals from, late admissions, 1962-1964 (Box 106, Folder 668 - 669)
  - Wood shop, 1957-1960 (Box 106, Folder 670 - 672)
  - Woodshop, 1960-1964 (Box 107, Folder 673 - 676)
  - Yale college: course of study committee - general, 1958-1959 (Box 107, Folder 677)
  - Yale college course of study committee - sophomore discussion groups, 1956-1959 (Box 107, Folder 678)
  - Yale college - course of study committee, 1959-1964 (Box 107, Folder 679 - 683)
  - Yale college - miscellaneous, 1958-1964 (Box 107, Folder 684 - 689)
  - Yale college orders, 1963-1964 (Box 107, Folder 690)
  - Allocations committee, 1939-1950 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Allocations procedure, 1950-1952 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Allocations class of 1954, 1951-1954 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Allocations 1952 - 1953, 1953-1954 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Allocations - transfers - etc., 1953-1954 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Allocations - class of 1953, 1950 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Allocations class of 1955, 1952 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Allocations 1956, 1953 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Allocations 1957, 1954 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Allocations, committee on class of 1958, 1955 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Allocations, committee on class of 1958 & 1959, 1953-1957 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Allocations, Comm. on class of 1960, 1956-1958 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Allocations '58 class of 1961, 1958-1961 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Allocations class of 1962, 1958-1959 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Allocations - class of 1963, 1959-1960 (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - Allocations - class of 1964, 1960-1961 (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - Allocations - class of 1965, 1961-1962 (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - Stiles & Morse, 1962 (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - College masters, council of, 1956-1958 (Box 110, Folder 19 - 20)
  - Dining Hall, 1958-1960 (Box 110, Folder 21 - 22)
  - Gymnasium, 1959-1962 (Box 110, Folder 23 - 25)
  - Old campus (Freshman Register), 1953-1957 (Box 110, Folder 26)
  - Program blank folder, 1956-1959 (Box 110, Folder 27 - 30)
  - On the Fence, 1955-1959 (Box 110, Folder 31)
  - Board of permanent officers freshman year - minutes, 1920-1934 (Box 111, Folder 32)
  - Committee on freshman rules, 1920-1928 (Box 111, Folder 33)
  - Committee on rules, 1928-1938 (Box 111, Folder 34 - 36)
  - Committee on rules - minutes, 1942-1945 (Box 111, Folder 37)
  - Committee on rules, 1942-1951 (Box 111, Folder 38 - 39)
  - Committee on rules, 1951-1956 (Box 112, Folder 40 - 41)
  - Freshman governing board, 1946-1954 (Box 112, Folder 42)
  - Exams, 1936-1938 (Box 112, Folder 43 - 47)
  - Exams, 1941 (Box 113, Folder 48 - 49)
  - Special examinations vouchers, 1931-1955 (Box 113, Folder 50 - 51)
  - Prep school lists, 1920-1949 (Box 114, Folder 52 - 61)
  - College lists, 1941, 1943 (Box 115, Folder 62 - 63)
  - Navy college lists, 1944 (Box 115, Folder 64)
  - College lists, 1944-1945 (Box 115, Folder 65 - 66)
  - College lists - Navy V - 12 summer term, 1943 (Box 115, Folder 67)
  - V - 12 statistics ca., 1943 (Box 115, Folder 68)
  - Navy V - 12, Navy statistics, 1943-1944 (Box 115, Folder 69)
  - V - 12 work sheet as of Nov. 30, 1944 (Box 115, Folder 70)
  - V - 12 course of study printed materials, 1943-1946 (Box 115, Folder 71)
  - V - 12 list of men leaving & marine to be screened, 1945-1946 (Box 115, Folder 72)
  - V - 12 lists of trainees expected to complete requirements for commissions, 1946 (Box 115, Folder 73)
  - Navy unit men to return as NROTC, V - 5 or as civilians, 1946 (Box 115, Folder 74)
  - Navy unit men to return as NROTC, V - 5 or civilians, 1946 (Box 116, Folder 75)
  - NROTC to NROTC, 1946 (Box 116, Folder 76)
  - Navy V - 12 bullentins, 1943-1946 (Box 116, Folder 77)
  - V -12 information, 1944-1945 (Box 116, Folder 78)
  - Navy V - 12 American history test of knowledge, 1944 (Box 116, Folder 79)
  - Health department notices on V - 12 unit, 1945-1946 (Box 116, Folder 80 - 81)
  - Honor system committee, 1920s (Box 117, Folder 82)
  - Cheating, cases of, 1930-1942 (Box 117, Folder 83)
  - Freshman week Mr Hall's statement, 1933 (Box 117, Folder 84)
  - Student riots, 1923-1928 (Box 117, Folder 85)
  - Outline in social science, 1925-1926 (Box 117, Folder 86)
  - Proposal curriculum, undated (Box 117, Folder 87)
  - Copy of memorial to Dean Walden from freshman governing board, 1937 (Box 117, Folder 88)
  - Tests from Mr Wittenborn, 1930-1940 (Box 117, Folder 89 - 90)
  - Orders for transcript copies, 1944-1945 (Box 117, Folder 91)
  - Form letters to prospective freshmen, 1920 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Blanks sent to prospective freshmen, 1920 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Mailing to prospective freshmen, 1921-1935 (Box 118, Folder 3 - 17)
  - Mailing to entering freshmen, 1936-1943 (Box 118, Folder 18 - 25)
  - Mailing to incoming freshmen, 1943 (Box 118, Folder 26)
  - Mailing to entering freshmen, 1944-1945 (Box 118, Folder 27 - 29)
  - Mailing to incoming freshmen, 1945 (Box 118, Folder 30)
  - Mailing to prospective freshmen entering fall, 1945 (Box 118, Folder 31)
  - Mailing to prospective freshmen entering 1945-1946 spring (Box 118, Folder 32)
  - Mailing to incoming freshmen, 1946 (Box 118, Folder 33)
  - Mailing to prospective freshmen entering spring 1947 (Box 118, Folder 34)
  - Room application blank for fall term for 1947 (Box 118, Folder 35)
  - Mailing to incoming freshmen, 1947 (Box 119, Folder 36)
  - Mailing to incoming 2nd term freshmen, 1948 (Box 119, Folder 37)
  - Mailing to incoming freshmen, 1948-1956 (Box 119, Folder 38 - 48)
  - Mailing to entering freshmen (May), 1957-1959 (Box 119, Folder 49 - 50)
  - May mailing - additional material, 1958-1959 (Box 119, Folder 51)
  - July mailing to entering freshmen, 1958 (Box 119, Folder 52)
  - Mailing to class of 1963, 1959 (Box 119, Folder 53 - 54)
  - Mailing to entering freshmen from the services, 1960 (Box 119, Folder 55)
  - Mailing to entering freshmen May, 1960 (Box 119, Folder 56)
  - Mailing to entering freshmen July 12, 1960 (Box 119, Folder 57)
  - First mailing to incoming freshmen May, 1961 (Box 119, Folder 58)
  - Forms I, II and III, 1920-1929 (Box 119, Folder 59)
  - Dormitory rules, 1920-1948 (Box 119, Folder 60)
  - Upperclass blanks (printed by other offices), 1920-1955 (Box 119, Folder 61)
  - Church attendance pledge & related material, 1921-1926 (Box 120, Folder 62)
  - Freshman calendar, 1921-1943 (Box 120, Folder 63)
  - Registration blanks, 1922-1937 (Box 120, Folder 64)
  - Room contract, 1922-1951 (Box 120, Folder 65)
  - Athlectic association, 1926-1948 (Box 120, Folder 66)
  - Freshman counselors, 1928-1942 (Box 120, Folder 67)
  - Freshman schedules, 1929-1950 (Box 120, Folder 68)
  - Freshman schedule (replaced forms I, II, III in 1930-31), 1930-1939 (Box 120, Folder 69)
  - Engineering counselor assignment, 1930-1943 (Box 120, Folder 70)
  - Dining halls - information sheet, 1932-1947 (Box 120, Folder 71)
  - Course of study program mailed to entering freshmen, 1935-1941 (Box 120, Folder 72)
  - Information sheet on electrical appliances & radios - university service bureaus, 1936-1947 (Box 120, Folder 73)
  - Band notices, 1938-1940 (Box 120, Folder 74)
  - Freshman intramural athletics, 1939-1947 (Box 120, Folder 75)
  - War blanks and bulletins, 1941-1946 (Box 120, Folder 76)
  - Navy V - 12, 1943-1945 (Box 120, Folder 77)
  - Material given to freshmen on entering, 1948-1951 (Box 120, Folder 78)
  - Material given to freshmen on entering, miscellaneous items from, 1926-1951 (Box 120, Folder 79)
  - Remedial reading record (same for 1954-1955), 1953-1954 (Box 120, Folder 80)